[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Think about where to go tomorrow.
The Summer Palace and the Temple of Heaven.
Which do you think is more fun?
Boss,
did you hire me just to be your tour guide?
You even got me a pager.
Honestly, with what you're paying,
you could easily hire someone
much more capable than me.
There are many types of secretaries.
You're the most naive one.
There's no such thing as a free meal.
It's just not time to work yet.
What's the rush?
Come on.
If you're going to copy someone, pick an expert.
The guy in the red hat is an out-of-towner.
Why are you watching him?
No,
I watched the people downstairs earlier,
they all mix it like this.
Brother Qi, why don't you try it first?
Do you sell salt for a living?
It's salty as hell.
No, it's...
I think this sauce is just like this.
When we get back,
come with me to look at cars.
You're pretty sharp, aren't you?
Shop around and
find the cheapest car dealership
in Minzhong for me.
Leave this to me.
What kind of car do you want?
Do you need a driver?
You know how to drive?
I don't.
My boyfriend does.
Are you kidding me?
A guy who pawned my watch?
Would he sell me out too?
I'll vouch for him.
He definitely won't do it again.
He wouldn't dare break the law.
Whether he'd dare to or not
sometimes depends not only on the cost,
but also on how high the stakes are.
Wipe the sauce off your mouth.
I'm talking about doing business.
Do you know what the most profitable business is now?
Military assets.
I'm not even talking about selling guns and bullets.
Just things like
socks, pants,
and work gloves.
Even tiny things can make a fortune.
Introduce me to your aunt.
Let's get rich together.
If I say no,
are you
going to fire me?
It's not impossible.
My aunt specifically said
not to discuss anything with outsiders lately.
They had a meeting.
Whoever talks gets in trouble.
Understood.
You have to zip your lips.
Xiaolu, he
also has many friends in the military.
And they know about military assets.
They're not local,
so there's no need for secrecy.
How's his driving?
Will he drive us into a ditch?
He used to drive for the government.
He won awards every year.
You won't find
a driver with better skills than him.
U-turns, going through tunnels,
and perfect parking...
he's an expert at everything.
His bonus will be the same as yours.
His salary will be slightly lower.
Deal?
We'll do whatever you say.
Boss, a toast to you.
Thank you, Boss.
What's that noise upstairs?
He's already asleep.
He's even started snoring.
Here, have some tea.
Why was the sauce at the hot pot place so salty?
I bet yours wasn't salty at all.
They all say you're honest,
but you're actually the worst.
Silently taking revenge.
Petty and vindictive.
I made you hold your pee,
so you put salt in my sauce.
Just to make me pour you tea.
I wouldn't dare.
If I couldn't even figure that out,
I might as well quit State Security.
Then what else did you figure out?
You like Jinlan.
Not in the slightest.
There are many ways to like someone.
Saying one thing but meaning another is one.
How do you fall asleep and wake up on command?
I think that beats tailing and wiretapping.
Being with you is really boring.
What else can I do but sleep?
Remember this.
In the future, especially during surveillance,
you must find someone interesting.
If you're boring yourself,
you need to find someone who tells jokes.
I get it.
Get what?
A partner is very important.
Partners, my ass.
Life is like this tea.
It's too bitter.
You have to learn to find your own fun.
Otherwise, how do you keep going?
Who ran these simulations?
These are the Americans' projections.
Do any of you know
how long it would take the PLA to land?
How long until they reach this very conference room?
How long?
Where are the guys from the "MIB"?
They're verifying the intelligence.
They'll be here shortly.
So many of us are waiting on them.
We're running out of time.
What's taking them so long?
Go hurry them up!
Yes, sir.
I'll get right on it.
In recent years,
across all fronts of our nation's military technology sector,
numerous role models have emerged.
Today,
the Comrades being commended
are the outstanding representatives of this.
Throughout the lives of everyone sitting here,
we have been working for the development and security of our motherland,
making silent contributions.
Especially recently,
regarding missile fuel technology,
those who have made significant breakthroughs,
the Comrades from Institute 761.
You have delved deep and bravely made breakthroughs.
With firm conviction
and relentless effort,
for China's defense industry,
you are composing a magnificent chapter.
I know who the snitch is.
Someone familiar?
It's not like this hasn't happened before.
It barely made a ripple.
Those due for a promotion still got it.
Did they really pull the list?
What's our department thinking?
Maybe we just put it on hold for now.
You're still young anyway,
and you have the credentials.
A year sooner or later won't matter much.
Who is it?
Engineer Cao.
The director is personally treating us.
He's taking everyone to Quanjude.
In ten minutes,
gather on the first floor.
I have an upset stomach.
I think I'll pass.
I'll go tell the director then.
Okay.
Didn't I just say
I...
Mr. Cao, your coffee.
I didn't order coffee.
Maybe your friend
or a colleague ordered it for you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Who's not going?
Everyone has to go.
Okay.
I'll go, I'll go.
I'll go.
I'll head down as soon as I'm dressed.
Hurry up.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Okay, okay.
You guys head down first.
Beijing Exhibition Center
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Are you alright?
Regarding travel reimbursement,
are there specific rules?
What do you mean?
I saw you choosing a taxi earlier.
Is there a difference between 1.20 and 1.40?
Obviously.
This is a Comrade's car.
This Erguotou,
is 56 percent ABV.
Thanks.
When we first came to Beijing for college,
everyone was from the north.
Old Jia and I were the only southerners.
Our class monitor was a Beijing local.
He forced us to drink Douzhi with him.
Oh, my god.
After just one sip,
I almost threw up on his shoes!
After drinking the Douzhi,
he took us to a public bathhouse.
Us southerners had never seen a body scrub before!
In a pool bigger than this private room,
there were tall, short, fat, and skinny guys,
all completely butt naked.
It was embarrassing as hell!
The funniest part was Old Jia.
He is extremely nearsighted,
so he went into the bathhouse wearing his glasses.
The lenses got completely fogged up.
When he wiped them clean and saw clearly,
he was scared silly.
He turned around and ran.
When he got to the door, he realized
he couldn't run any further.
If he kept running,
he'd be running onto the street butt naked!
We laughed so hard!
Come, come.
Mr. Jiao is here to toast everyone!
I heard you all before I even walked in,
cheering louder and louder.
How much have you had?
You're drinking faster than our table!
Colleagues,
today is a great day for us.
On behalf of Institute 761
and the Party Secretary,
I'd like to toast you all.
Come on, cheers!
Thank you, sir.
Please, drink up.
Thank you, sir. Thank you, sir.
Engineer Jia,
are we going to a bathhouse after these drinks?
I'll go if he goes.
Mr. Jiao is coming to toast again.
I actually need to talk to you about something.
I might need to delay my return by a day.
Can you help me change my flight ticket?
This needs to be reported in advance.
I am telling you before boarding.
Isn't telling you now considered "in advance"?
We really can't just change it on a whim.
The boss set the schedule.
Well, the boss is right here.
Just go tell him and it's settled.
I'll pay for the ticket myself.
Out of my own pocket.
So I can change it, right?
This person is too sensitive.
I'll go handle him.
Let me, let me, let me.
Liaoping, have you lost your mind?
The boss was just here
and specifically emphasized
that we must stay together as a group.
And why is that?
For confidentiality.
Nobody is singling you out.
Why are you getting so agitated?
Let me explain it to you nicely.
Explain what?
What, are you going to report me?
Bring me down,
so you think you can take my place?
Is that it?
Wipe the dirt off your own face first before you talk.
Boss, there are so many foreigners.
Brother Qi.
Who do you think he's here to meet?
I have a hunch.
He's not here to make contact.
It's a smokescreen.
A smokescreen?
To fool who?
Sis Li.
Why is he back here again?
Let's wait and see.
Hello.
Hi.
I'll have a coffee with extra sugar.
Okay. Will you be sitting...
I'll be sitting over there.
Alright, please wait a moment.
I'll bring it over to you shortly.
Thank you.
Confucius said, "A man without trust,
I know not what he can accomplish."
I'm here.
You're heading back tomorrow.
If I were your colleague,
I'd also go out to buy some souvenirs,
and enjoy the coffee here.
There's a jacket on the counter.
The size should fit you perfectly.
Do you see it?
Okay, okay.
Your coffee, sir.
Thank you.
Xiao Wang,
you keep watch here.
I'll go in and take a look.
Boss.
What can I do?
However many people are here,
exchange business cards with every one of them.
Do what you do best.
Okay.
Sorry. Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Once in Beijing, let's not meet again.
You need to be a moving target.
If there's a mantis,
let them focus on you, the cicada.
An innocent cicada.
If I play the cicada,
what will the mantis think?
How will he know if I'm clean or not?
I mean, what if...
That won't happen.
You just need to tell yourself
that you're a tourist on a business trip.
Just act natural.
Go sightseeing and shopping,
make friends, and do business.
Why are you everywhere?
What a coincidence!
When did you arrive?
Was it the same day as me?
Right?
What day was that, Boss Lin?
Mr. Ma.
Let's go.
You're always where the leaders are.
You shouldn't be in business.
You should be in politics.
His brother-in-law taught him all that.
A leader is like a tree.
Fruits just keep dropping from this tree.
Aren't you gonna catch them?
Our pockets are too small.
They're too big to catch.
And we wouldn't dare compete with you.
Just dealing with medical equipment
is enough to feed the two of us.
Computed tomography scanners,
MRI scanners.
Aren't there enough in Minzhong?
You had to come all the way to Beijing.
And you claim your appetite isn't big.
Your boss...
never tells the truth.
So sly.
You promised me a slice of the pie.
What are you guys really up to?
You tell me.
Medical equipment leasing.
What Brother Qi mentioned...
Like what?
Mr. Ma,
what you said last time at Hope Primary School...
you weren't bluffing, were you?
If you want to cooperate, you've got to show your hand.
379 Military Hospital.
Even hospitals have to balance their books.
Trade-ins.
As long as it pays off.
An approval from the Health Bureau.
One from Beijing works.
Would one from Minzhong work?
Anywhere works.
Alright.
Mr. Ma.
I know you're not short on money.
Are you operating collectively or as decentralized franchises?
For an operation this size,
I might not be good at much else,
but I definitely have practical experience with franchises.
Let's have a good chat when we get back.
Sounds good.
When are you heading back?
As soon as I'm done here.
How many tickets?
One.
I'm alone too.
Why don't we share a rental?
Beijing is even drier than I imagined.
I've got phlegm in my throat.
And I get nosebleeds at night.
It's like that for everyone at first.
You'll be fine in a couple of days.
Choosing a place like this to meet
for a VIP like you,
although it's for security reasons,
still feels a bit disrespectful.
To be honest,
I didn't expect you to come.
Nor did I think you'd dare to.
I said we'd meet in person,
so we meet in person.
Even if I get caught,
or executed,
even if I die in Beijing,
my time in this business wouldn't be in vain.
Missile deployment is like a tree.
I can only give you one branch,
the thickest and most crucial one.
As for how the rest of the tree grows,
you'll have to piece it together yourselves.
We deal with theoretical research.
Based on my personal speculation,
our technology is quite mature.
But a full upgrade will still take time.
It hasn't reached the set combat parameters.
Let me translate that.
Does this mean the current drill
is just a drill?
How should I put it?
From a scientific perspective,
without a hundred percent certainty of success,
it's better not to fight.
Your intel is like a box of matches.
I'm going to use it to light a pack
of wet explosives.
If we guess right, everything will be fine.
But if we guess wrong,
it will ignite a war.
Scientific data is absolute.
But many wars in this world happen by chance.
What do you mean?
I don't want a war.
I don't think you do either.
At least the two of us,
neither of us wants
what falls on this lake to be
a missile instead of leaves.
Broadly speaking,
on behalf of the common people,
and on a personal level,
on behalf of my family,
my old mother, my wife,
and my dog at home,
I thank you.
Please, please, please.
Get up.
You in person
are quite different
from the man I imagined.
I'm too big of a target.
Next time we meet,
I might find a runner
to go back and forth between us.
What kind of person is he?
Someone you can trust.
Someone you don't need direct contact with.
This person will assist and protect you.
Whenever you need him,
he will appear.
This
is your salary for three months.
I've signed for it on your behalf.
Top Secret intelligence.
Mobilize all resources
to verify it immediately.
One, two, three, four!
Understood.
This is for you.
I'm the best in the world.
No one can outdrink me.
Really.
I totally don't...
To be honest with you,
before this,
Xiao Lu didn't believe me either.
I drank him under the table,
he passed out right there.
Alright, you did great today.
I've been...
You really can hold your liquor.
drinking since I was a kid.
Don't you doubt it.
When I was little, my grandma
would dip a chopstick in it
and put it right in my mouth.
"Have a taste."
"Is it good?"
It's always been like that.
Do you know where the room is?
Here.
This way.
Drinking since childhood...
Slow down.
Excuse me.
I got it.
After you, Boss.
Boss.
Did you know?
This time,
Even the exhibition director's card,
I managed to get it.
Let me show you.
Here.
This...
is from Beijing.
I've got a whole stack of them.
This one is...
from within the province.
This one is from Xiamen.
I heard on the radio a few days ago,
someone publicly stated in the US,
talking about "Two Chinas."
Weren't we aiming for peace?
He wants Taiwan independence!
Did you know that?
I'm on my own anyway, so it doesn't matter.
But with your big family,
do you still dare to go to Beijing?
What makes a politician?
They say what people want to hear,
and spin lies to fit the occasion.
Otherwise, why travel all that way?
He publicly supported reunification before.
He won't really push for independence.
It's just noise.
Just do your own job.
Don't overthink the rest.
I'm not afraid.
What are you afraid of?
And there's Yang Chunyang, Liu Chunyang...
Also from Shenzhen.
This one...
I kind of forgot.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you a little worried?
Boss, where are we...
Where are we going tomorrow?
We're heading back tomorrow.
We're heading back tomorrow?
We still have a few days.
Are you alright?
I'm going to the restroom.
Young man,
may I ask you something?
Do you know where the luggage storage is?
I don't know. Probably outside.
Thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am the chief purser for this flight.
Our aircraft has reached cruising altitude.
The captain has turned off the seatbelt sign.
However, while seated,
we still recommend keeping your seatbelt fastened.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am the chief purser for this flight.
Our aircraft has reached cruising altitude.
Hello.
May I borrow your newspaper?
Here you go.
Thank you.
They were all gone when I tried to get one.
You're welcome.
Over a decade ago,
on the mainland,
those who could pick up broadcasts from Taiwan, China,
would occasionally hear Taiwan, China
sending coded messages to their sleeper agents.
These coded messages
usually used four-character codes
to transmit orders.
And later, spies from Taiwan, China on the mainland
will continue to receive such coded messages.
I heard you went home with heatstroke.
How are you feeling?
It's easy to handle as long as there's medicine.
Just one step away.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you ask me to find evidence?
I'll have it very soon.
Brother Qi just went back to the office.
That's how I found out you were back.
I was just passing by your place after work.
If you haven't had dinner yet,
let's grab a bite.
Is... is something the matter?
I might be getting transferred soon.
Well?
Even if he's totally drunk,
or incredibly scheming,
or a massive fraud,
we got the money anyway.
What are you afraid of?
If I knew he'd pay us in advance,
I should've asked for two more months.
He wants to hire you,
and he wants to hire me too.
But why?
Think about it.
I'm practically a nobody.
His watch was so expensive,
yet he didn't call the police.
He paid to get it back himself.
He's obviously playing a game.
What game?
People don't do things for no reason.
Does he just want my driving skills?
Or your secretarial skills?
What do you mean?
Just say what you mean.
Do I even need to spell it out?
I already know what he's up to.
Don't play dumb.
I recognize that Taiwanese businessman.
He gave me a tip before.
Bro, I can tell you're a big boss.
You look great.
The kind who definitely makes a fortune every year.
Bro, if you could look out for me,
and give me some money for smokes,
you'll make another fortune by the end of the year.
The thing is, I can't pee with you doing this.
Others might not recognize you,
but I do.
Being a big boss is tough.
I just started peeing,
and when you grabbed me,
I peed on my shoe.
I'm sorry.
These shoes are very expensive.
A friend brought them from the US to Taipei,
and I wore them from Taipei to here.
You can't even buy them with money.
They cost a few thousand.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, boss.
I'm sorry, my mistake.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Well, aren't you going to wipe them?
Brother,
you need shoe polish.
Wiping them like that won't work.
This is genuine leather.
Do you think you're scrubbing a toilet?
I'll go buy some right now.
I'll be quick, very quick.
Wait a minute.
No need, no need.
I have some, boss.
Just kidding.
Did I scare you?
He's an old fox.
He's rich,
and lives all by himself.
Don't you think he has his own schemes?
I wasn't talking about you.
I was talking about him.
What if he has his own ideas?
You're just afraid he'll steal me away.
If you cared about me,
you should just say so.
If you don't care,
we'll see if I ever talk to you again.
He wants to use my aunt's connections
to do business in military assets.
What military business?
That's obviously a roundabout scheme.
He never had good intentions to begin with.
My home is on Xiangyang Street.
Two blocks west of here,
just around the corner.
If Huadong hadn't told me you lived here,
I wouldn't have known I pass your house every day.
Huadong said he's looking to rent too.
He wants to be closer to work.
He might be looking around here too.
Maybe.
Two days in Beijing and your accent changed.
How was it? Was Beijing fun?
Why do you want to leave?
Is it your own choice,
or orders from above?
Boss, two more skewers of this.
Okay, coming right up.
I don't know why I'm always hungry lately.
Working overtime makes you hungry easily.
Have you guys been busy lately?
Didn't you ask me to find evidence?
Almost. I can't say much right now.
But I'm sure
there's definitely something wrong with him.
All right.
Let's see who's faster, you or me.
I might go into surveillance.
Full-time.
Wouldn't that mean joining a task force?
Which unit?
Is it still in our division?
After working all day,
I don't want to say a single word I'm allowed to,
and I can't say what I actually want to.
Isn't that annoying?
That doesn't suit your personality.
I'm actually pretty used to it.
Living like I'm mute and deaf.
To be honest, working a job like this,
don't you get sick of it?
Growing up,
nobody ever asked me what I wanted to do,
or what I could do.
My dad is a primary school teacher.
He thought being a teacher was good.
My mom is a nurse.
She thought being a doctor was good.
But actually, I didn't like either.
I just wanted to be a soldier.
But after I enlisted,
I realized
I wasn't suited to be a soldier at all.
Who said you weren't suited for it?
Squad leader, platoon leader, company commander...
They all said so.
But the more they said it,
the more I wanted to prove myself.
Later, I went to study military medicine.
I just wanted to stay
and prove them wrong to the end.
And now?
What do you think you're suited for?
Intelligence or recon?
Being the spear or the shield?
Wasn't I the one asking the questions?
How come you're asking me now?
You really shouldn't leave.
You're the most talented among all of us.
Brother Qi said so.
What about you?
What do you think I'm most suited for?
I think you're suited for anything.
If I had to pick a partner for surveillance,
I'd definitely pick you.
I wouldn't do it.
You're too tight-lipped.
You went to Beijing,
and didn't even say if the roast duck was good.
If I partnered with you for surveillance,
I'd be bored to death.
Actually,
once you get to know me,
I can be quite talkative.
I'm just afraid you'll find me too chatty.
You really are a strange person.
What do you mean?
You're hard to read.
I can't figure you out at all.
I am Wang Kai,
inviting you to watch the drama
"Confrontation".
Throwing intel around just like that...
What happens to us if they blow their cover?
If they're going to play their hand,
then we'll arrest every single
gambler at the table.
Initiate ahead of schedule,
Operation Spring Thunder No. 1.
From now on,
the target Ma Qi's team is watching
will be wiretapped by Jin Lan.
Officially open the case
and place them under close surveillance.
Your cover identity
is a tour guide at Shenzhou Strait Travel Agency.